Finding Aid for the Tony Barrett Papers PASC.0061
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 3. Unproduced script material, clippings, and correspondence
  - Danger Inc. script by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - The Fugitive notes and script pages, 1963 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Pat Steele script by Tony Barrett and Lewis Reed, 1961 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Vic Steel notes and script by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 122, Folders 5-6)
  - Story ideas, undated (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - LA Times article "Surgery Ends Sex Identity Riddle", 1970 October 25 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Smokejumper research, 1960-1961 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - San Francisco and Point Richmond research, 1969 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - "The Joseph Jacobs Handbook of Familiar Jewish Words and Expressions", 1957 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - "When Gypsies Gather at Appleby Fair", undated (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Cruise brochures and a map of the Moon, 1965-1966 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Variety article "Songs Start with Title, Says [Al] Kasha", undated (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Surfing research, 1964 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Violent crime clippings, 1972 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Jurgensen's grocery flyer for 1970 Bordeaux, undated (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - "Elephants Don't Remember, Says Circus Trainer", undated (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - Astrology guides, 1963 (Box 123, Folder 15)
  - Australia research, 1970 (Box 123, Folder 16)
  - Jokes, 1972-1974 (Box 123, Folder 17)
  - Motorcycle clippings, 1965 (Box 123, Folder 18)
  - Check kiting clippings, 1972 (Box 123, Folder 19)
  - Prison clippings, 1971 (Box 123, Folder 20)
  - Gambling clippings, 1970 (Box 123, Folder 21)
  - LA Times article "LA Airport Customs Jam", 1972 December 3 (Box 123, Folder 22)
  - Van de Camp's 50th anniversary clippings, 1965 (Box 123, Folder 23)
  - Stella Ceja and Mando Ramos article, 1970 November 1 (Box 123, Folder 24)
  - Limited production auto makers article, 1972 October 8 (Box 123, Folder 25)
  - Rene's restaurant, Woodland Hills article, 1973 March 30 (Box 123, Folder 26)
  - Diamonds research, 1973 (Box 123, Folder 27)
  - Imitation diamonds research, undated (Box 123, Folder 28)
  - Earthquakes and insurance, 1971 (Box 123, Folder 29)
  - FBI reports, 1954-1962 (Box 123, Folder 30)
  - History of Hollywood by First Federal Savings and Loan, undated (Box 123, Folder 31)
    Also includes Screen Actor magazine, 1965 September-October.
  - "3 Plead Not Guilty in Plot against Mayor", undated (Box 123, Folder 32)
  - Gardena poker clubs article, 1971 March 28 (Box 123, Folder 33)
  - Hollywood Blvd. article, 1972 April 16 (Box 123, Folder 34)
  - John Rotz article, undated (Box 123, Folder 35)
  - "Law and Courts in the News" pamphlet, 1960 (Box 123, Folder 36)
  - Laws in California clippings, 1973 (Box 123, Folder 38)
  - Lobbyist notes, undated (Box 123, Folder 39)
  - "Court Ruling Gives New Rights to Parolees", 1972 October 8 (Box 123, Folder 40)
  - Congressional perquisites clipping and notes, undated (Box 123, Folder 41)
  - Pornography raids clipping, undated (Box 123, Folder 42)
  - Police training clippings, 1972 (Box 123, Folder 43)
    Also includes an LAPD memo about the unauthorized wearing of police uniforms and regalia.
  - Mayoral race clippings, 1973 (Box 123, Folder 44)
  - Mail service clipping, undated (Box 123, Folder 45)
  - Swank restaurants article, undated (Box 123, Folder 46)
  - The Neighbors by William Wood, 1970 September 29 (Box 125, Folder 1)
- Series 4. Bound scripts
  - Burke's Law vol. 1, 1963 (Volume BLW 0001)
    Includes: WHO KILLED BILLY JOE?; WHO KILLED ANNIE FORAN?' WHO KILLED WHAT'S-HIS-NAME; WHO KILLED MARTY KELSO?; WHO KILLED MY GIRL?; cast lists.
  - Burke's Law vol. 2, 1964 (Volume BLW 0002)
    Includes: WHO KILLED THE TALL ONE IN THE MIDDLE?; WHO KILLED THE HORNE OF PLENTY?; WHO KILLED THE SURF BROAD?; WHO KILLED THE SWINGER ON A HOOK?; WHO KILLED ROSIE SUNSET?
  - Burke's Law vol. 3 / Amos Burke: Secret Agent, 1965 (Volume BLW 0003)
    Includes: WHO KILLED THE RABBIT'S HUSBAND?; WHO KILLED MR. COLBY IN LADIES' LINGERIE?; THE WEAPON; NIGHTMARE IN THE SUN; A LITTLE GIFT FOR CAIRO; A VERY IMPORTANT RUSSIAN IS MISSING.
  - The Felony Squad vol. 1, 1966-1967 (Volume FEL 0001)
    Includes: THE STRANGLER; TARGET!; A BLUEPRINT FOR DYING; THE FEAR MERCHANT;THE DEATH BAG; LET HIM DIE!; THE 30-GRAM KILL; THE PAT HAND OF DEATH; WHO'LL TAKE CARE OF JOEY?
  - Mod Squad vol. 1, 1967-1968 (Volume MSQ 0001)
    Includes: THE TEETH OF THE BARRACUDA; THE GURU; THE UP TIGHT TOWN; MY, WHAT A PRETTY BUS; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 2, 1968 (Volume MSQ 0002)
    Includes: GUESS WHO'S COMING TO MURDER; BAD MAN ON CAMPUS; CAPTAIN GREER CALL SURGERY; WHEN SMITTY COMES MARCHING HOME; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 3, 1968 (Volume MSQ 0003)
    Includes: YOU CAN'T TELL THE PLAYERS WITHOUT A PROGRAMMER; A TIME TO LOVE -- A TIME TO CRY; THE PRICE OF TERROR; FIND TARA CHAPMAN!; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 4, 1968 (Volume MSQ 0004)
    Includes: LOVE; A QUIET WEEKEND IN THE COUNTRY; THE SUNDAY DRIVERS; A GIRL'S BEST FRIEND; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 5, 1968 (Volume MSQ 0005)
    Includes: FLIGHT FIVE DOESN'T ANSWER; SHELLGAME; FEAR IS THE BUCKING HORSE; A REIGN OF GUNS; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 6, 1969 (Volume MSQ 0006)
    Includes: A HINT OF DARKNESS, A HINT OF LIGHT; CHILDREN OF SORROW, CHILDREN OF LIGHT; A RUN FOR THE MONEY; KEEP THE FAITH, BABY' production documents..
  - Mod Squad vol. 7, 1969 (Volume MSQ 0007)
    Includes: A SEAT BY THE WINDOW; PEACE NOW - ARLEY BLAU; RIDE THE MAN DOWN; THE GIRL IN CHAIR NINE; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 8, 1969 (Volume MSQ 0008)
    Includes: AN EYE FOR AN EYE; MY NAME IS MANOLETE; A PLACE TO RUN, A HEART TO HIDE IN; TO LINC -- WITH LOVE; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 9, 1969 (Volume MSQ 0009)
    Includes: CONFRONTATION; THE HEALER; LISA; THE DEATH OF WILD BILL HANNACHECK; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 10, 1969 (Volume MSQ 0010)
    Includes A PLIGHT UPON THE LAND; NEVER GIVE THE FUZZ AN EVEN BREAK; IN THIS CORNER -- SOL ALPERT; SWEET CHILD OF TERROR; production documents
  - Mod Squad vol. 11, 1969 (Volume MSQ 0011)
    Includes: THE KING OF EMPTY CUPS; A TOWN CALLED SINCERE; THE DEBT; THE EXILE; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 12, 1969-1970 (Volume MSQ 0012)
    Includes: SURVIVAL HOUSE; MOTHER OF SORROW; THE DEADLY SIN; A TIME FOR REMEMBERING; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 13, 1970 (Volume MSQ 0013)
    Includes: RETURN TO DARKNESS, RETURN TO LIGHT; CALL BACK YESTERDAY; SHOULD AULD ACQUAINTANCE BE FORGOT; THE LOSER; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 14, 1970 (Volume MSQ 0014)
    Includes: THE LONG ROAD HOME; SEARCH AND DESTROY; WHO ARE THE KEEPERS, WHO ARE THE INMATES? "A" IS FOR ANNIE; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 15, 1970 (Volume MSQ 0015)
    Includes: SEE THE EAGLES DYING; A FAR AWAY PLACE SO NEAR; WELCOME TO THE HUMAN RACE, LEVI FRAZEE!; THE SONG OF WILLIE; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 16, 1970 (Volume MSQ 0016)
    Includes: JUST RING THE BELL ONCE; THE ACTIVIST; SUFFER, LITTLE CHILDREN; A TIME OF HYACINTHS; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 17, 1970 (Volume MSQ 0017)
    Includes: FEVER; THE JUDAS TRAP; IS THERE ANYONE LEFT IN SANTA PAULA?; KICKS, INCORPORATED; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 18, 1970 (Volume MSQ 0018)
    Includes: A BUMMER FOR R.J.; A DOUBLE FOR DANGER; THE HOT HOT CAR; IS THAT JUSTICE?; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 19, 1970-1971 (Volume MSQ 0019)
    Includes: THE COMEBACK; WELCOME TO OUR CITY; WE SPY; THE PRICE OF LOVE; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 20, 1971 (Volume MSQ 0020)
    Includes: COLOR OF LAUGHTER, COLOR OF TEARS; THE SANDS OF ANGER; SURVIVAL; PIGEON WITH A BROKEN WING; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 21, 1971 (Volume MSQ 0021)
    Includes: ...AND A LITTLE CHILD SHALL BLEED THEM; THE MEDICINE MEN; EXIT THE CLOSER; THE SENTINELS; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 22, 1971 (Volume MSQ 0022)
    Includes: CRICKET; WILD WEEK-END; THE POISONED MIND; DEATH OF A NOBODY; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 23, 1971 (Volume MSQ 0023)
    Includes: JIGSAW; THE LOSER; FEET OF CLAY; I AM MY BROTHER'S KEEPER; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 24, 1971 (Volume MSQ 0024)
    Includes: KILL GENTLY, SWEET JESSIE; DEAL WITH THE DEVIL; SHOCKWAVE; NO MORE OAKS FOR ERNIE HOLLAND; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol.25, 1971-1972 (Volume MSQ 0025)
    Includes: THE CAVE; OUTSIDE POSITION; THE TANGLED WEB; BIG GEORGE; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 26, 1972 (Volume MSQ 0026)
    Includes: THE CONNECTION; THE THUNDER MAKERS; EYES OF THE BEHOLDER; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 27, 1972 (Volume MSQ 0027)
    Includes: SANCTUARY; TAPS - PLAY IT LOUDER; YESTERDAY'S ASHES; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 28, 1972 (Volume MSQ 0028)
    Includes: THE FUR COAT OF DEATH; GOOD TIMES ARE JUST MEMORIES; ANOTHER FINAL GAME; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 29, 1972 (Volume MSQ 0029)
    Includes: CRIME CLUB; CORBEY; CAN YOU HEAR ME OUT THERE; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 30, 1972 (Volume MSQ 0030)
    Includes: BELINDA - THE END OF LITTLE MISS BUBBLE GUM!; THE TWAIN; KRISTIE; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 31, 1972 (Volume MSQ 0031)
    Includes: RUN, LINCOLN, RUN!; CHILD OF A CHILD; PUT OUT THE WELCOME MAT FOR DEATH; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 32, 1972 (Volume MSQ 0032)
    Includes: AND ONCE FOR MY BABY; DEATH IN HIGH PLACES; SCION OF DEATH; production documents.
  - Mod Squad vol. 33, 1972 (Volume MSQ 0033)
    Includes: THE NIGHT HOLDS TERROR; CRY UNCLE; production documents.
  - Peter Gunn vol. 1, 1960-1961 (Volume PGN 0001)
    Includes: BULLET FOR A SHIELD; BABY SHOES; THE BEST LAID PLANS; A BULLET FOR THE BOY; BULLET IN ESCROW; THE CANDIDATE; COME DANCE WITH ME -- AND DIE; THE CROSSBOW; CRY LOVE...CRY MURDER; DEADLY INTRUSION; THE DEADLY PROPOSITION; DEATH ACROSS THE BOARD; THE DEATH FRAME.
  - Peter Gunn vol. 2, 1958-1961 (Volume PGN 0002)
    Includes: DEATH IS A FOUR LETTER WORD; DEATH IS A RED ROSE; DEATH IS A SORE LOSER; THE DEATH WATCH; THE DIRTY WORD; DREAM BIG, DREAM DEADLY; THE DUMMY; EDGE OF THE KNIFE; THE BLACK DOLL; FILL THE CUP; THE FUSE; THE GRUDGE; THE HEIRESS.
  - Peter Gunn vol. 3, 1959-1961 (Volume PGN 0003)
    Includes: THE JUDGMENT; KIDNAP; KILL FROM NOWHERE; LAST RESORT; LETTER OF THE LAW; THE LONG GREEN KILL; THE LONG, LONG RIDE; MASK OF MURDER; FLY AWAY HOME; THE MURDER BOND; THE MURDER CLAUSE; THE PASSENGER.
  - Peter Gunn vol. 4, 1958-1961 (Volume PGN 0004)
    Includes: A PENNY SAVED; PORTRAIT IN LEATHER; THE PRICE IS MURDER; PROTECTION; THE RIFLE; ROUGH BUCK; THE ROYAL ROAST; SEE NO EVIL; SEND A THIEF; SEPI; SHORT MOTIVE; SING A SONG OF MURDER.
  - Peter Gunn vol. 5, 1959-1961 (Volume PGN 0005)
    Includes: A SLIGHT TOUCH OF HOMICIDE; SPELL OF MURDER; TAKE FIVE FOR MURDER; A TENDER TOUCH; TERROR ON THE CAMPUS; ...THAN A SERPENT'S TOOTH; 'TIL DEATH US DO PART; WINGS OF AN ANGEL; WITNESS IN THE WINDOW; THE WOLFE CASE; THE YOUNG ASSASSINS.
  - Radio vol.1, 1952-1956 (Volume ASR 0001)
    These are episodes Barrett wrote rather than just acted in.
    Includes scripts for: Hollywood Star Playhouse; Escape; Romance.
  - Radio vol. 2, 1953-1956 (Volume ASR 0002)
    Includes scripts for: Yours Truly, Johnny Dollar; Tales of the Texas Rangers; O'Hara; One Stage; Roy Rogers; Mabel Stark.
  - Television vol. 1, 1956-1961 (Volume AST 0001)
    Includes scripts for: Straightaway; The Investigators; The New Adventures of Charlie Chan.
  - Television vol. 2, 1955-1961 (Volume AST 0002)
    Includes scripts for Straightaway; Flight; Casablanca.
  - Television vol. 3, 1957-1960 (Volume AST 0003)
    Includes scripts for: Tightrope!; Union Pacific; Steve Canyon.
  - Television vol. 4, circa 1954-1958 (Volume AST 0004)
    Includes scripts for: Silent Service; Public Defender; State Trooper.
  - Television vol. 5, 1955-circa 1960 (Volume AST 0005)
    Includes scripts for: Mr. Lucky; O'Conner's Ocean; Highway Patrol.
  - Television vol. 6, circa 1953-1958 (Volume AST 0006)
    Includes scripts for: Colt .45; The Californians; Action in the Afternoon.
  - Television vol. 8, 1966 May 18 (Volume AST 0008)
    Includes screenplay Himalaya.
  - Television vol. 9, 1955-1963 (Volume AST 0009)
    Includes scripts for: The Untouchables; Mr. Domino; County General; Nemo!; G.P.; The Fugitive.
  - Television vol. 10, 1955-1957 (Volume AST 0010)
    Includes scripts for: Rin-Tin-Tin; Johnny Nighthawk; Treasury Men in Action.
  - Television vol. 11, 1958 (Volume AST 0011)
    Includes scripts for: Wanted Dead or Alive; Boots and Saddles; Rough Riders.
  - Television vol. 12, 1955-1967 (Volume AST 0012)
    Includes scripts for: Ironside; Guns of Will Sonnett; The Count of Monte Cristo; Barefoot Boys.
  - Television vol. 14, 1957-1965 (Volume AST 0014)
    Include script for: The Rogues; unbroadcast pilots; Not for Hire; Schlitz Playhouse; Casey Jones; unproduced stories.
  - Television vol. 15, 1969 (Volume AST 0015)
    Includes scripts for The Monk; shooting schedule.
  - Television vol. 16, 1966 (Volume AST 0016)
    Includes scripts for: The Girl from U.N.C.L.E.; A Man Called Shenandoah; Wait for Dark.
  - Television vol. 17, 1963 (Volume AST 0017)
    Includes scripts for 77 Sunset Strip.
  - Television vol. 18, 1953 (Volume AST 0018)
    Includes scripts for Johnny Dollar.
  - Television vol. 19, 1967 (Volume AST 0019)
    Includes scripts for: Garrison's Gorillas; Chrysler Theatre.
  - Television vol. 20, 1967-1968 (Volume AST 0020)
    Includes scripts for: It Takes a Thief; The Survivors.
  - Television vol. 21, 1961-1963 (Volume AST 0021)
    Includes scripts for: The Dick Powell Show; The Richard Boone Show; unbroadcast pilots.